[provides food services]
[give the purchase price. Noblee, a supplier of specialised refined oils and fats]
[provide the South Afrcian unit with future technical support, and products makde under that agreement will continue]
[give it access]
[give Pioneer Sugar shareholders a price equivalent, gives a premium of 91 pct over Pioneer's last reported net tangible assets per share, CSR said. CSR said the generous offer price reflects the cost savings which will flow from integrated management of CSR's and Pioneer's raw sugar mills and building materials businesses. These economies can only be achieved through CSR control and management of Pioneer Sugar, it added. The takeover announcement came soon after CSR's earlier reported statement that it will sell its Delhi Petroleum Pty Ltd unit]
[give them 35 pct each. REUTER]
[provide underwriting information services]
[give a foreign oil company a dominant position in Canada's oil industry. Imperial Oil is already Canada's largest energy company, with 1986 revenues of 7.1 billion Canadian dlrs. Chicago-based Amoco had 1986 revenues of 20.23 billion U.S. dlrs. Its Amoco Canada Petroleum subsidiary is 100 pct owned by Amoco Corp.]
[provide Roach with 50 mln U.S. dlrs of financing]
[give it ownership of 35 pct of the outstanding stock. Dynamics said the price of stock under the option, exercisable]
[gives Redland the choice of accepting the CSR offer]
[provides, provide increased mortgage and lending services and enable the company]
[provide equipment, service and distribution suppoort]
[provides regularly scheduled service out of Dallas/Fort Worth Regional Airport as an affiliated carrier of AMR Corp  and had revenues in 1986 of 14.1 mln dlrs.]
[provide bridge financing of up]
[give serious consideration]
[provide a major boost...For chanelling investment between Spain and the European Community," the statement said. "This operation enables us]
[provide the necessary capital, provide a marketing outlet]
[provides kits]
[provide the equity portion of the offer by contributing at least 125 mln dlrs in cash and Taft Broadcasting common, Narragansett said. It said the group has been advised by First Boston Inc's First Boston Corp that the investment banker is "highly confident that financing]
[give the selling price. Proceeds will be used]
[provide capital loss coverage and indemnify Standard Pacific against undisclosed liabilities. Reuter]
[give Sosnoff a majority interest on a fully diluted basis, the arrangement of sufficient financing]
[give the companies six months]
[gives it a "major ownership position" in Sanchez, which specializes in software products]
[gives Hearst its biggest newspaper holding in Texas, where the California-based publisher already owns papers in San Antonio, Beaumont and Laredo. The chain also owns, among others, the flagship San Francisco Examiner, the Los Angeles Herald Examiner and the Seattle Post-Intelligencer.]
[give it control. Warburg said it reserves the right, provide its shareholder list]
[provide him equal representation with the current board. DNA also said it will submit a proposal at its annual meeting]
[provide further details later.]
[give a reason. Kresge is the forerunner of what is now the K Mart chain. The name was changed]
[provides coin-operated laundry services, building maintenance services and retail office and furniture operations. In fiscal 1986, Allegheny reported earnings from continuing operations of 8.2 mln dlrs or 1.09 dlrs a fully diluted share, excluding income of 59.7 mln dlrs from discontinued operations and an extraordinary loss of 8.1 mln dlrs. In May 1985, Allegheny sold its Pepsi-Cola Bottling Co unit]
[provide it with confidential information given]
[give former Bard shareholders control of the combined company. Bard makes tennis and squash racquets and accessories.]
[give permission soon.  This is the first time a Japanese bank has bought a stake in a Portuguese bank. Sanwa plans]
[give details of the loan]
[give terms of the sale. In addition, Avalon said three other directors resigned. It said Benjamin W. Macdonald, a director of TMOC Resources Ltd, the principal holder of Avalon stock, and Hardwick Simmons, a vice chairman of Shearson Lehman Bros Inc, were then named]
[give Nippon Life a ringside seat and possibly lower commissions on Wall Street, where it invests an increasing percentage of its assets of 90.2 billion dlrs, they said. Nippon Life staff will also acquire expertise in business sectors which have not yet opened up in Japan, they added. The agreement between the two companies calls]
[give KDI an option]
[provide products]
[provides software]
[give it broader distribution of its corporate relocation service and mortgage programs.]
[provides a suitable extension]
[give the owners control of 16 pct of the French telephone switching market, sources close]
[give Venezuela an additional outlet]
[give further details. Bank of America's West German branch lost some 32 mln marks in 1985. The result includes profit and loss transfers from Bankhaus Centrale Credit and the Visa organisation. The sale of the units is part of the bank's worldwide restructuring plan. REUTER]
[provide it with information subject]
[provides specialty insulation installation and asbestos removal services. J.M. said all of its directors except Jack E. Manning Jr. have resigned and Myers and Morgan were named]
